and I do
e
n't know if my kids' forum is
no sé si el foro de mi chavalería está
already up it's not up I don't know what
ya levantado no está levantada no sé lo
was going on but I say it's
que estaba pasando pero yo digo está
doing a [ __ ] crazy thing it's
haciendo la [__] locura o sea se ha
become a real
convertido en una auténtica biblioteca
sanse library or a kind of
del sanse o una especie de biblioteca
salsero library everyone is there I mean it was
del salsero todo el mundo está allí o
going well before I have a question have you
sea antes iba bien tengo una duda alguna
ever put a video in trends and
vez has colado un vídeo en tendencias y
in what positions just curiosity
en qué posiciones es curiosidad
greetings mastodon machine venom
un saludo máquina mastodonte venom
many times javier in fact for all
muchas veces javier de hecho para todo
jupiter thank you very much king in fact my
júpiter muchas gracias rey de hecho mi
box that is if it was because when the
cuadro que es si fue porque cuando la
wing michu fight the eixo
pelea de wing michu el vídeo del eixo
win michu adalah video my video the video that I
win michu adalah mi vídeo el vídeo que
made talking about the subject well it was
hice hablando sobre el tema pues era el
number 3 it was in 3 and 4
número 3 estuvo en el 3 y en el 4 en
trending in fact
tendencia de hecho estaba el vídeo de
win's video was said in trending 1 2 was the
win dicho en tendencia el 1 el 2 estaba
dallas one I do
el de dallas
n't know if 3 we were will heller out of
no sé si el 3 estábamos will heller de
airplay and I
out airplay y yo
think that I think it's whatever the
creo que creo que es lo que no sea el
order but we were and we're changing
orden pero estábamos y vamos cambiando
July thank you very much and in fact that
julio muchas gracias y de hecho en esa
week with the three videos that I made in
semana con los tres vídeos que hice en
trend 11 am in good position in  the
tendencia 23 am en buena posición en el
34 armor 51 no the other day one of the
34 armor 51 no el otro día uno de los
last live shows that was
últimos directos que irse estaba en
trending too it's a little low it was
tendencia también está bajito estaba el
40 around there but yeah a lot of videos a lot of
40 por ahí pero sí muchos vídeos muchos
videos from both the main channel and the
vídeos tanto del canal principal como
secondary channel a lot I wouldn't know if
del secundario muchísimo no sabría de si
they were from memory but I do remember
los de memoria pero me acuerdo de
some cases in particular because
algunos casos en particular porque
man for example there's a top guy who says it
hombre por ejemplo es un top que dice
was face in reverse and he's still on
que era face in vuelto y está todavía en
my channel his name is 5 youtubers who
mi canal se llama 5 youtuber a los que
attacked something like that it was about the big
agredieron algo así era sobre la gran
bomb that snuck into trend it was my
bomba ese se coló en tendencia fue mi
first video with a lot of views then I
primer vídeo con mucha visita luego
'm talking about goyo the video a
estoy hablando de goyo el vídeo un
million and a half views
millón y medio de visitas
then this week calypso welcome
luego en esta semana calipso bienvenido
in that same week with the three videos
en esa misma semana con los tres vídeo
that I made talking about the topic that had
que hice hablando del tema que tuvieron
six hundred thousand seven hundred thousand
los de seiscientas mil setecientas mil
views each and then they pose with the
visitas cada uno y luego posan con las
many videos sanz colas a lot of videos
muchos vídeos sanz colas muchos vídeos
the second debate he did with dallas
el segundo debate que hizo con dallas
was trending on the secondary channel there have
estuvo en tendencia del canal secundario
been a lot of videos trending on the
han estado muchísimos vídeo en tendencia
secondary channel which is doing very well and
al canal secundario que va muy bien y
from the main channel some some can't
del principal de algunos algunos no sabe
say from memory I think when the
decir a la de memoria creo que cuando la
movie is on the wind vitro also gets
peli está the wind vitro también se mete
into trend it took a lot  there was a lot going on
en tendencia se llevó mucho hubo mucho
with the page me kids dotcom it's
lo de la página me chavalería puntocom
going really well it's going [ __ ] great okay but it
va muy bien va de [__] madre vale pero
's gone from having like 100 between 60 and
ha pasado de tener unos 100 entre 60 y
100 users connected simultaneously it's
100 usuarios conectados simultáneamente
worth about 50 thousand visits a day to having
vale unas 50 mil visitas al día a tener
sixty something seventy something
sesenta y tantos setenta y tan también
daily visits and about 600 seven hundred
visitas diarias y unas 600 setecientas
people connected simultaneously all
personas simultáneamente conectadas todo
day long okay so that's [ __ ] crazy
el día vale entonces una [__] locura
okay [ __ ]
vale
great I was hoping this page would
de [__] madre yo esta pagina esperaba
crash I know the truth I was hoping it would go
que peta sé la verdad esperaba que fuera
well but I mean sayas it went down today it went
bien pero osea sayas ha caído hoy se ha
down I don't know if it was with attacks or with
caído no sé si ha sido con ataques o con
or with weight so ivan is there
o con peso entonces el iván está ahí
touching it and he's changing the server he
tocándola y está cambiando el servidor
's putting in a more powerful server I don't
está poniendo un servidor más potente no
know what move hasn't been made there it's been
sé qué movida no se ha hecho ahí lleva
late to the kid it's been all day the
tarde al chaval lleva todo el día el
kid
chaval
and you need the page it's been a
y necesitas la página ha sido una
great girl out there they want to
grandiosa de chica por ahí me la quieren
plagiarize it but forget it forget it
plagiar pero olvidaros olvidaros
forget it
olvidaros
and I want to remind you that not only is the
y quiero recordaros que no solamente la
page not only about salsa I mean
página no solamente es de salsero o sea
the majority of time detectors in the sal had
que la mayoría detector tiempo en el sal
surgery why don't you download more but in
se operó por qué no bajáis más pero en
the forum there is a section  of salt or
el foro hay sección de sal se o sección
politics section music section
de política sección de música sección de
television section okay by the way I'm in today
televisión vale por cierto ya entre hoy
tomorrow no more obviously
mañana por hoy ya no evidentemente
tomorrow I have to create the channel with
mañana me tengo que crear el canal con
Lorena to comment on the reality shows they have
lorena para comentar los reality que
planned and the one about temptations and
llevan pensada y la de las tentaciones y
we have to launch the channel I don't know
tenemos que estrenar el canal no sé
yet what it's going to be called send my
todavía cómo se va a llamar mandar mi
ideas for a name
ideas de nombre
on twitter and on instagram send me ideas
en twitter y en instagram mandarme ideas
what name we both come up with it's going to be
que nombre nos ponemos los dos va a ser
a channel to comment on reality shows okay
un canal de comentar realities vale
send my idea we have no impunity
mandar mi idea que no tenemos impunidad
what name to give it and we have it because
qué nombre ponerle y lo tenemos que
tomorrow I have to create it okay and
mañana ya lo tengo que crear vale y
well then I send this theater
bueno pues más mando a este teatro
directly from those him and he says those him
directo de esas él y dice esas él
talking about doors to the basement I don't have a
hablando de puertas al sótano no tengo
[ __ ] clue do you want door to the basement alex
ni [__] ya quieres puerta al sótano alex
cool a good friend of mine
guay que un coleguilla mío buena gente
works imitating michael jackson has
trabaja imitando a michael jackson tiene
the best job in his [ __ ] life
el mejor trabajo de la [__] vida
the guy works giving a show
el tío trabaja dando show haciendo
being michael's double
siendo el doble de michael
alex
álex
blanco what is called lengua de blanco
blanco que se llama lengua de blanco
literally
literal
hello javi in ​​the end what happened with me I don't
hola javi al final qué pasó con yo no
have the absolute one to give you the roulette
tengo la absoluta para darte la ruleta
nothing more greetings
nada más saludos
thanks thank you very much well in case
gracias muchísimas gracias bueno por si
someone takes it behind
alguien la coge detrás ya estuve
explaining two or three days ago
explicando hace dos o tres días
that I made the decision to stay on
que tome la decisión de quedarme en
YouTube
youtube
because I liked the platform for a
porque me gustaba en la plataforma hacía
while I hadn't been liking it very much
tiempo que no me estaba gustando mucho
with this you know okay [ __ ] great
con esto en you know vale de [__] madre
with the team they have always treated me
con el equipo me han tratado siempre
great okay but in the end what I have
genial vale pero al final lo que he
said many times I am my own boss
dicho muchas veces yo soy mi propio jefe
and it's stupid to be in one place when I
y es tontería estar en un sitio cuando
prefer to be somewhere else so I came
prefiero estar en otro entonces me vine
here now I'm staying here so if I am a
aquí ya me quedo aquí entonces si soy
member or whatever I did not renew because I
miembro o lo que sea no renové ya porque
am no longer there
ya no estoy allí
with an iPhone it does not let me become a member face
con iphone no me deja hacer miembro cara
begging face begging face
mendigando cara mendigando cara
begging well you have to leave
mendigando pues se tiene que dejar
catering because I have an iPhone and I
catering porque yo tengo iphone y me
become a member all the cars and when
hago miembro todos los autos y cuando
I want so look you see what
quiero así que mira ves qué
[Music]
[Música]
simply without wanting to start being
simplemente sin querer empezar a ser
direct here on YouTube to see how it
directo aquí en youtube para ver cómo
was and the best is much more is much
iba y la mejor está mucho más está mucho
cooler
más guay
this is possible it seems better to me to do it
esto se puede se me hace mejor hacerlo
only on YouTube ok what six
solamente en youtube ok lo que seis
members there well if you want to become members
miembros allí pues si queréis haceros
here if you do not want then do not
aquí miembros si no queréis pues no lo
do it but I would not wait because no no I have
hagáis pero no me esperase porque no no
already announced it in fact here the endorsement
ya lo he anunciado de hecho aquí el aval
to the administration that I have  left
a la administración que lo he dejado
worth a machine a machine is to give it a
vale un máquina un máquina es darle ua
'machine management okay now that I did
'gestión máquina vale ahora que hice
those the one tells me to let him go and his
esas el de me dice dejarlo libre y su
girlfriend tells him that he doesn't play at all
novia le dice que no juega nada
ainhoa ​​welcome axel great genius
ainhoa la bienvenida axel grande genio
next to the biggest team fan in
al lado del mayor seguidor de equipo de
history
la historia
what do they contribute to the part let's see more of
qué aportan al parte vamos a ver más a
alberto 98 for sure very
alberto 98 seguro
sure me me
segurísimo
according to what he said provoked that you buy
según ha dicho provoque que te compras
into the team series on the other hand he
en la serie de equipo por otra parte
has also provoked that
también ha provocado que se han comprado
many others have been bought he
muchas otras
says like that the jeme has nothing to do
dice así el jeme no tiene nada que hacer
with the shirt
en la camiseta
well they are
bueno
very difficult I do
son muy difíciles
n't know if having a shirt of the plague
no sé si tener una camiseta de la peste
but he came from the street and they put
pero el vino de la calle y le pusieron
pins on him that they won't be sons of [ __ ] but
bolos que no serán hijos de [__] pero
as if he already came with a name from the street
como que venía ya con nombre de la calle
to another level of another level because anyway
a otro nivel de otro nivel porque en fin
or cats are the only data that this
o gatos son único los datos que éste
trash demands he is talking about cats and
tacho demanda está hablando de gatos y
video consoles minute 9 50 when to
de videoconsolas el minuto 9 50 cuando
start there I [ __ ] the host
empezar por ahí me cago la [__]
[Music] I am
[Música]
going to dedicate myself
me voy a dedicar
and I regret that a law on my side
y lamentó que a una ley de mi lado
a stone
una piedra
and then talking about video games is
y luego estar hablando de videojuegos es
tremendous
tremendo
what moves the channels have  of
qué movidas tienen los canales de
video games is also or is not this there is no
videojuegos también es o no es esto no
this in the language and there is a group of
hay este en la lengua y hay un grupo de
channels for all types of content that is
canales para todo tipo de contenido que
not that they are gamers or are they not having played
no es que sean gamers o sean ellos no
a few times but
haber juega unas veces pero por lo
generally what it does is to make them inform
general lo que hace es hacerles informar
and give their opinion and it is like salt was operated on
y opinar y ya es como sal se operó de
video of video consoles ok to trust and
vídeo de videoconsolas vale a fiar y
they have a salt has mounted one with
tienen un sal se ha montado lo uno con
the others also that it is curious
los otros también que es curioso
how the yoke that they are
como el yugo que se les son
watts was
watts
understood part 5 it was a walkie how
se entendió parte 5 era un walkie qué
bad I feel called from the walkie to the
mal me siento llama del walkie a la
leblanc or he calls it you walk and why
leblanc o lo llama a you walk y por qué
imitate michael jackson because he
imitar a michael jackson porque se
dresses up michael jackson he calls it
disfraza michael jackson lo llama hay
walking
walking
to me as a fan of michael jackson the
a mí como fan de michael jackson la
truth is it really pisses me off that they
verdad me toca muchas pelotas que lo
call it you walk and you know why there is a
llamen a you walk y sabes porque hay un
walkie it is
walkie es
a kingdom meme that you offend me either
un meme reino que me ofendas tampoco
but call it you walk and because he
sabe pero llamarlo a you walk y porque
dresses up as michael jackson then
se disfrace de michael jackson entonces
everyone who goes to me that they are already the iwork
todo el que vaya me que ya son el iwork
the walkie was a figure I don't know what museum
el walkie era una figura no sé qué museo
from zero I don't know what the [ __ ] horrendous that is  I
de cero no sé qué [__] horrenda que se
supposed it was you loved me or although it didn't
suponía que era me querías o aunque no
look anything like it
se parecía en nada
when he asked Javier Beirán to
cuando le pidió a javier beirán que
make a video but in it he
hiciese un vídeo pero que en la llevó
already asked him but he Javi Javi
que ya le ha pedido pero él javi javi
Oliveira by the way there's no need to
oliveira por cierto tampoco hace falta
ask Javier Oliveira to
que se le pida a javier oliveira que me
make a video for me because haha
haga un vídeo porque ja
to me he hasn't asked me for a
a mí el ale a mí no me ha pedido cada un
video I don't know if we have
vídeo yo no sé si directamente hemos
spoken directly or if I have ever asked him
hablado o le he preguntado yo alguna vez
something about a post about something that I will be
algo sobre algún post sobre algo que me
missing about your content
faltará sobre vuestro contenido
but coming like this is that we have not
pero el venir así es que no hemos
spoken as such about salt he never in
hablado como tal de salz él nunca en
private I think that
privado
some I think on some
creo que alguna creo que en alguna
occasion if perhaps having consulted
ocasión si acaso el haber consultado
something where I can find this this
algo dónde puedo encontrar esto esto
how it was what is the context of this
cómo fue cuál es el contexto de esto
I imagine that I cannot
me imagino que eso no te lo puedo
guarantee you a little because it has been
garantizar un poco porque ya hace
a long time since he dealt with issues of the
muchísimo tiempo que no trató temas del
jail issue but coming to ask
tema de cárcel pero el venir a pedirme a
me to make a video how to do that
mí que haga un vídeo cómo hacer eso
called the channel reyes del reality or
llamada al canal reyes del reality o
something like that face crying with laughter lollipop lollipop
algo así cara llorando de risa piruleta
lollipop thanks the manual for
piruleta piruleta gracias el manual por
the idea and for the super chat reyes del
la idea y por el súper chat reyes del
reality it seems very to me I don't know
reality se me hace muy no sé
reyes del reality  I'm
reyes del reality
sure there's some other
seguro que hay algún otro nombre más
funnier name or something I don't know I would
divertido o algo no sé
n't know what to do because more people
no sabría qué hacer porque más gente
leave that oliveira it's true that guy is the
eso deja de oliveira es cierto ese tipo
worst on youtube the
de lo peor de youtube
worst on youtube well I don't like
de lo peor de youtube pues tampoco me
it either
tira qué
but the 7 I don't know how many videos I've already
pero el 7 no sé cuánto vídeo ya me he
made javi one day I put a comment
hecho javi un día le puse un comentario
there to be an [ __ ]
ahí para dar por culo
take
toma
he's a clown last year he spent time
él es un payaso el año pasado se pasó
throwing [ __ ] and lying there are
tirando [__] y mintiendo sobran las
five left and kissing up to
cinco y haciéndole la pelotilla a saco a
xbox so they would give it to him not even xbox I don't care
xbox para que se la regalase ni xbox
about him for being toxic he made a fool of himself
paso de él por tóxico quedó en ridículo
worldwide you
a nivel mundial
can say the same without insulting and
puede decir lo mismo sin insultar y
also do
también sea
n't send your hanger insulting I've
no manden su percha insultando lo he
said it a ton of times okay and I'm not
dicho ya un montón de veces vale y no lo
saying it anymore man I'm not saying it anymore I don't want to
digo más tío no lo digo más no me quiero
get even with you guys because in the end I'm
pagar con ustedes porque al final no soy
nothing without you but do me a favor
nada sin ustedes pero hacerme el favor
goddess your hanger to turn out
diosa su percha para resultar
okay
vale
toxic people of [ __ ] it's over here on
gente tóxica de [__] se acabó aquí en
this channel
este canal
you can criticize the same thing with a joke or
puedes criticar lo mismo con un chiste o
something funny and not insult and to
con algo gracioso y no insultar a y por
the face okay I don't know the move let's see sal he
la cara vale no sé la movida a ver sal
likes the salsero that like that
se le gusta el salsero eso así
literally the same one is
literalmente sea el mismo lo está
saying it to me  put a comment to
diciendo que me puso un comentario para
click what's going on because my
pinchar qué es lo que pasa porque mis
content is to be fischer boel salcedo
contenidos es ser fischer boel salcedo
the controversy and if they come and click on me then
la polémica y si vienen y me pincha pues
take 7 videos there are two ways I don't do it
toma 7 vídeos hay dos maneras no lo hago
as a personal grudge or to screw
a modo de inquina personal ni para
him or to lose subscribers
joderle ni para que pierda suscriptores
or for privacy it's to do I do it
ni para la intimidad es hacer lo hago
to create a week this machine
por crear una semana esta máquina
had dedicated a video to me where the
me había dedicado un vídeo en donde el
title said that I was an idiot like
título ponía que yo que era [__]
that
así
and to the face the guy without knowing him nobody
y por la cara el tío sin conocerlo nadie
always says that I say and that's that I do
siempre dice eso digo y eso es que yo
n't know that doesn't sound familiar to me I am the one who put a
eso a mí no me suena yo soy que puso un
title
título
that was the first video that I made for him
que fue el primer vídeo que le hice que
yes to a title in bad taste been
sí que a un título de mal gusto estado
other times for changing it
otras veces por cambiarlo
thanks or so g
gracias o sea g
what was cesar zelandia laughs at the
qué fue césar zelandia se ríe de la
death of a child you are disgusting which
muerte de un niño das asco que también
is also unpleasant and manual thank you very much
es desagradable y manual muchas gracias
king who is also also in very bad
rey que también es también en el muy mal
taste and very rude the title of
gusto y muy mal educado el el título de
chevalier be like I recognize it you are worth
chevalier sea en plan lo reconozco vales
very free it is very free but
muy gratuito es muy gratuito pero hace
three years ago churra the sars in three years
tres años churra el sars en tres años
you know it does not occur to me to put
sabes no se me ocurre a mí poner otra
a title like that again  for the face it's okay but he
vez un título así por la cara vale pero
always says and from opus that I
es que siempre dice y de opus que yo
made a video where I put the title you are an
hice un vídeo donde puse el título eres
idiot
[__]
I don't know if maybe this video had
yo no sé si a lo mejor este vídeo tenía
another title Andy and I changed it when
otro título andy y yo le cambié cuando
he told me but it doesn't sound familiar to me from
él me lo dijo pero yo no me suena de
February that's it no he doesn't mess with anyone
febrero eso está no no se mete con nadie
and this one is going for him I don't know
y éste va por él
who peso tanos is yes yes yes I know what it is he does he
no sé quién es peso tanos sí sí sí yo sé
's quite a pain in the ass and
que es hace él es bastante tocapelotas y
toxic
tóxico
it's that it doesn't sound familiar to me the deposed
es que a mí no me suena el depuesto
idiot in a title he always
[__] en un título él siempre lo
says it but I don't remember I don't know if it's that I don't know if I
dice pero yo no me acuerdo no sé si es
could know
que no sé si podría saber
if maybe the video was that
si a lo mejor el video fue ese el
first and that he would put it and then I would
primero y que se lo pondría y luego lo
remove it but it doesn't sound
quitaría yo pero es que no me suena a la
true to me you know that I recognize
verdad ustedes sabéis que yo reconozco
things okay if I had put it I
las cosas vale si lo hubiera puesto
could so in two ways and audio
podría así que de dos maneras y audio
that it is an ugly title and put you disgusting
que es un título feo y poner das asco
okay be ugly
vale sea feo
but at that time we were more stupid
pero en aquella época éramos más burro
than now okay yes now we are stupid at
que ahora vale sí ahora somos burros en
that time even more have
aquella época más todavía
been presented
se han presentado
and I only for a comment that I
y yo nada más que por un comentario que
put since then he  Javier and this
le puse desde entonces él javier y este
kid has a rage that has a deep affection there
niño tiene una rabia que tiene un cariño
were divided the gift of the beard that
había divididas el don de la barba que
of YouTube because they put that on me
de youtube porque me ponen eso
[Laughs]
[Risas]
and I have rage I don't like you very much
y yo tengo rabia no me cae muy bien
honestly the little that I've seen of you has
sinceramente lo poco que he visto de ti
been all the times that I've been
ha sido todas las veces que he estado
informing me to record videos and to
informando me para grabar vídeos y para
compile already see well just fallen the
recopilar ya ver bien nomás caído la
truth made comment that you send me
verdad hecho comentario que me mandes
pleases a lot
agrada mucho
then in person you are different and then
luego en persona eres diferente y luego
one day well I see you there on the beach
un día pues te veo por ahí por la playa
no that we are Andalusians we have a
no que somos andaluces nos tomamos la
beer who knows but
cerveza quién sabe pero
[Music]
[Música]
but that you have rage is not a thing of the
pero que tengas rabia no es una cosa del
internet show and another thing is already whatever it is
show de internet y otra cosa es ya lo
one thing an internet thing do not
que sea una cosa una cosa de internet no
have personal rage what I saw although
tenga rabia personal yo lo que vi aunque
mentally a lot of the shrimp I do not remember
mente mucho la gamba yo no me acuerdo ya
by heart what it was
de memoria que es lo que fue
the things that I criticized but I know that there was
las cosas que critique pero sé que hubo
a video where he did climbs and talked
un vídeo donde hacía escaladas y hablaba
about things about video consoles that was very
de cosas de videoconsolas que era muy
easy to contrast look I am not
fácil de contrastar mira que yo no soy
an expert in video consoles when
un experto en videoconsolas cuando
we were when I was young yes I was
eramos cuando era joven sí que lo era
but now
pero ahora no
things like the loading screen
cosas como lo de la pantalla de carga
as saying that Kingdom Hearts was
como diciendo que el kingdom hearts era
the first  time in kingdom hearts that
la primera vez en el kingdom hearts que
the protagonist of the games was called
el protagonista de los juegos se llamaba
goku
goku
the hours came out in each world
las horas salía en cada mundo
characterized with the characters
caracterizado con los personajes
disguised when it was a lie since the
disfrazados cuando era mentira desde el
1 I already did it I had screwed up now that I
1 ya lo hacía había cagado ahora que yo
have anger
te tengas rabia
does not happen
no ocurra
I know that there was a misunderstanding I know that there
yo sé que hubo un malentendido yo sé que
was a misunderstanding that
hubo un malentendido que
in one of the videos in one of
que en uno de los vídeos que en uno de
the videos he made a comment like
los vídeos me puso un comentario como
I was messing with his partner or that
que yo me metía con su pareja o que
they answered him in a video I do not
ellos le contesté en un vídeo no me
remember which one it was
acuerdo cuál fue
I would never do that was your partner
jamás haría yo eso fue que tu pareja
was involved in a controversy for a
estaba metida en una polémica por un
comment that made something like that and I know that I
comentario que hizo algo así y sé que
commented or that I made a comment that the
comenté o que hice un comentario que la
hand I said oh how unpleasant that he is
mano dije oh qué desagradable que esté
on the microphone talking eating his
en el micrófono hablando comiendo su
pain they did not support me but it was
dolor no me apoyaron pero fue una
[ __ ] I would never do anything to
chorrada jamás haría algo por ofender de
really seriously offend a partner if you see
verdad en serio a una pareja si ve
fighting being with you not obviously
peleando estando contigo no obviamente a
you to your loved ones to hurt
tú a tus seres queridos para hacer daño
then first of all they do not like
entonces primero que no les gustan las
people to do anything personal I already think that
personas hacer nada personal ya creo que
in fact in one of the seven videos that I
de hecho en uno de los siete vídeos que
made I think it was giving him reason in
le hice creo que fue dándole la razón en
something I
algo
think there were videos
creo que hubo vídeos
in this I support those he I
en esto apoyo a esas él
think it was because  they shot
creo que fue porque lo balearon de
tweets for some [ __ ] ally is
tweets por una gilipollez aliad es
created was me oit then objective that
creado fue yo oit entonces objetivo que
sometimes to be a little bit me or
algunas veces a ser un poquito yo o lo
whatever [ __ ] great but of course it does
que sea de [__] madre pero por supuesto
n't go outside of youtube or what I have it
no va afuera de youtube ni de tengo
inclines almost nobody to very little okay
inclina a casi nadie a muy poco vale
but one thing on youtube we are already in
pero una cosa en youtube ya estamos en
the personal life
la vida personal
problem dedicates a lot of video the panting
problema dedica mucho vídeo el jadeo
oliveira I don't know in each in each video I get
oliveira yo no sé en cada en cada vídeo
worse I
voy a peor
mean if I am a degenerate I am worse than
o sea si soy un degenerado soy peor que
satan in each tremendous video I think I
satanas en cada vídeo tremendo yo creo
challenged them to a debate and he didn't come I would
que los rete un debate y no vino
not rent them no [ __ ] idea
ya no los rentaría ni [__] idea de por
where the discussion was going but I think I
dónde iba la discusión pero yo creo que
challenged him to a debate
lo rete a un debate
in one of the last videos and I think
en uno de los últimos vídeos y creo que
the good videos I know I know I know I know I know look I
los vídeos buenos
made
ya sé ya sé ya sé ya sé mira yo le hice
this video many years ago
este vídeo hace muchos años
dancing because I don't know why he didn't
bailando porque yo no sé por qué no me
make the video putting the
hizo el vídeo poniendo el título del
team title there and that's it I didn't talk about him anymore
equipo allá y ya está no hable más de él
until two years later when he left a
hasta dos años después que él me puso un
comment and this video hit him he hit him
comentario y este vídeo le pegó le pegó
in this video that [ __ ]
una en este vídeo que te cagas
in this video he gave it a review but
en este vídeo le dio un repaso pero
okay okay okay  because I made this
bueno bueno bueno porque le hice este
video because in a video that I made I
vídeo porque en un vídeo que hice
provided some d
proporcione algo de d
according to a football betting page
de acuerdo a una página de apuestas de
or it brought us down but it was something that
fútbol o nos bajoneó pero era algo que
he told me that is prohibited or is
me dijo él eso está prohibido o es de
class
clase
as long as the eggs bring me all the
en tanto los huevos tráeme todos los
eggs the comments box and I did
huevos la caja de comentarios y yo hice
potomac
potomac
and then later he
y entonces después
came and put something else on me
vino y me puso otra cosa
and then I told him to shut up
y entonces le dije yo que te calles
now I don't remember the order of
ahora no me acuerdo del orden de las
things
cosas
no more flight of things then that I do
ya no más vuelo de las cosas luego que
n't remember because the move was also
no me acuerdo porque movida fue también
the person in the person but I do
la persona en la persona pero sí que
remember this video that can't be the one that
acuerdo de este vídeo que no puede ser
he believes that he asked me to the ex who
el que él crea que me lo pidió al ex que
didn't ask me but he did defend it
no me lo pidió pero sí que defendía al
is why he
es por qué
had comments here ugly I
tuvo comentarios aquí feo
mean he had a comment from the ugly sacer
o sea tuvo comentario del sácer feo
towards leh and towards another kid
hacia leh y hacia otro chaval
referring to the way of speaking
refiriéndose a la forma de hablar
canarias nose of whatever I want that one that I also do
canarias nariz de lo que me dé la gana
n't know why they have put it
ese que tampoco sé por qué lo han puesto
really is right
realmente tiene razón
this well we would have to see who he is
esto pues habría que ver a quién se lo
saying it to because at least someone
está diciendo porque a lo menos alguien
who has come touches the balls
que ha venido toca los [__]
for nothing
para nada
efe
efe
but that the rain that the rent life
pero que la lluvia que el alquiler vida
javier liguera that makes me a  video walk
javier liguera que me haga un vídeo walk
and he's late now he already
y llega tarde ya els ya él
says nicolás savio liberia neither clicks nor
dice nicolás savio liberia ni pincha ni
cuts on youtube
corta en youtube
what
what
Jorge Javier from youtube dirty the
el jorge javier de youtube ensucia
internet with the pink sauce well go on what
internet con la salsa rosa pues anda que
you following is like
ustedes siguiendo es así
super white content not everything now I do
contenido super blanco no de todo ahora
n't have enough transcendence to be
no tengo la suficiente trascendencia
worth it to me that I
como para que me merezca la pena que yo
think that's why I stopped
creo que por eso haya dejado de
dedicating myself to the video I
dedicarme el vídeo
don't have much I don't make much noise
no tengo mucho no hago yo mucho ruido
because there are many people who have made I
porque hay mucha gente que me ha hecho
don't know how many more videos have made I don't know
no sé cuántos vídeos más ha hecho no sé
how many videos and it's like you
cuántos vídeos y es como
remember that you had said that in the tan
recuerdas que habías dicho que en la tan
the vaccine would arrive in 2040 in a live
llegaría la vacuna en 2040 en un directo
in which you played phallus gays well it
en el que jugabas falo gays pues ha
arrived first in costa rica
llegado primero a costa rica cara
smiling face with sunglasses lollipop I don't
sonriendo con gafas de sol piruleta no
remember having said the software and
me acuerdo de haber dicho el software y
in what context they would say it and why
en qué contexto lo dirían y por qué
when I was playing fall guys when
cuando estaba jugando a fall guys cuando
working at full guys we
trabajando a full guys
were confined I do
estábamos confinados
n't remember I don't know why bravos I don't know
no me acuerdo no sé por qué bravos no sé
if it was seriously a joke
si era en serio broma
in fact the directors are not or
de hecho que los directores no están ni
their life or anything
su vida ni nada
that is not so that it uploaded I only made
eso no es tan que subió solamente hice
a video on this channel  Nobel was the
un vídeo en el canal este nobel fue el
last video I made on the channel and I would
último vídeo que hice en el canal de y
n't watch it and I have the channel abandoned let's
no vería y tengo el canal abandonado a
see if I can get
ver si me pongo
close to some youtube group that
arrimarme algún grupo de youtube que me
invites me to something
inviten a algo
and it's that you've made four videos for
y es que me has hecho cuatro vídeos es
me it's that you've made 20 videos for me it's that you've
que me has hecho 20 vídeos es que me has
done I don't know what and how to see this is
hecho no sé qué y el cómo a ver esto es
a channel of controversy and of salt or that
un canal de polémica y de sal se o que
uploads videos on my two channels have
sube vídeos en mis dos canales tienen
content every day if not some the
contenido todos los días sino algunos el
other is worth it or rather in the live shows
otro vale o sea en los directos
kid three or four hours every
chamaquito tres o cuatro horas todos los
day of which there were two or three
días de los cuales hubo dos o tres
extracts every day you have to
extractos todos los días tienes que
count I upload videos every day that
contar yo subo vídeo todos los días que
there's something that I like to comment on
hay algo que a mí me guste para comentar
the main channel normally a video
el canal principal normalmente un vídeo
every two or three or two or three days and you are
cada dos o tres o dos o tres días y sean
welcome
bienvenidos
if you are involved in controversy first
si estás metido en polémica lo primero
if metal and he is dedicating tweets to me he
si metal y me está dedicando tweets me
is attacking me in live tweets and
está atacando en tweets en directo y
serious value would Jorge Javier like to
valor grave le gustaría a jorge javier
have your art churra to his face smiling
tener tu arte churra a cara sonriendo
with sunglasses well yes well yes the
con gafas de sol bueno sí bueno sí la
truth is yes why is he not going to win
verdad que sí para que no va a ganar
if first if you are in controversy
si lo primero si tú estás en polémica
with others  youtube I'm going to
con otros youtube yo aquí lo voy a
comment on it here if during the year is if during
comentar si durante el año es si durante
the last three or four months you're in
los últimos tres o cuatro meses estás en
40 controversies then I'll make 40 videos
40 polémicas pues yo sacaré 40 vídeos
about you as long as you slander us
sobre ti mientras que nos calumnie
defame us or anything like that great
difame ni nada de eso de [__] madre
then if on top of that you're dedicating yourself to me
luego si encima tú me estás dedicando tú
and you're dedicating live videos to me you're
y me estás dedicando directos me estás
dedicating videos to me I don't know what it is it's
dedicando vídeos no sé qué es que es
normal because I'm not talking about those
normal porque no estoy hablando de esas
he has been doing for a year and a half or two years
él desde hace un año y medio o dos años
which was the last video two years I think to
que fue el último vídeo dos años creo
make the last video to return or
que hacer el último vídeo volver o por
lastly it was like in March of last year
último fue como en marzo del año pasado
because he doesn't make noise anymore with his
pues porque no hace ruido ya con sus
themes of video games they fight over
temas de los videojuegos se pelean por
one of the play they fight over one of the
uno de la play se pelean por uno del
team he doesn't know how much and I don't know about that
equipo no sabe cuánto y a mí eso no me
subject you know I have
el tema sabe yo yo he hecho vídeo es
made videos it's to do when when you have to make criticism for something that has gone very viral for something a big mistake you know that although I consider it big but they ignored it I didn't dedicate so many videos to him now then why don't I make videos Alexis because he doesn't get into controversy but those
porque no se mete en polémica pero los
who get into controversy are normal on this
que se meten en polémicas normal en este
channel on this channel there are videos no  it's a
canal en este canal hay vídeos no es una
vaccine it's a medicine with side effects
vacuna es un medicamento con efectos
but it doesn't also scare me man that in
pero no me también hombre miedo que en
this channel in my channels I
el en este canal en mis canales yo
work every day and I make three or
trabajo todos los días y hago tres o
four hours of content if the topic
cuatro horas de contenido si el tema que
there is you it's this youtuber who is
hay eres tú es este youtuber que la está
messing it up that as it is then it comes out okay no well
liando que tal cual pues sale vale que
no because I have no one
no pues no porque yo tienen a nadie
personal or go after anyone or anything like that
personal ni vaya por nadie ni nada por
but now a lot of other youtuber and a
pero ahora otro mucho youtuber y otra
lot of other gossip about things that happen
mucha habladuría de cosas que sucedan
between those people
entre esa gente
talking about something I haven't
de hablar de algo no
lost them totally lost
la he perdido les perdió totalmente las
track of playing video games it would be on
pistas de jugar a videojuegos sería en
tweet I'm not going to tweet
tweet yo no me voy a tweets
not for nothing if only playing
no por nada si solamente jugar a
video games yes but it's that I'm not going to
videojuegos sí pero es que yo no voy a
never I'm going to make content that is
nunca voy a hacer un contenido que sea
only when there were balls I do
solamente cuando había huevos
n't think so because because I like
no lo creo porque porque a mí me gusta
sanse or I like to be chatting and telling
el sanse o me gusta estar charlando y
the possibility
contando la posibilidad
and having an event because they are going to
y habiéndome evento porque me van a
handle me for two days
manejar dos días
I am here well I chose youtube today
yo esté aquí bien yo elegí hoy a youtube
and now we have here a time of
y ahora tenemos aquí una época de
our life that will be on youtube
nuestra vida que será en youtube
and I suppose it will be quite serious because
y supongo que será bastante grave porque
here I am [ __ ] great
aquí yo estoy de [__] madre a mí es que
I like this format of the
me gusta el formato este de los directos
most  that where I was I like it here it
más que donde estaba a mí me gusta aquí
looks [ __ ] great it looks high quality
se ve de [__] madre se ve alta calidad
they are iron their perch the members
están iron su percha los miembros
kids I tell you I
chavales yo digo
tell you that there
os lo digo
are 12 thousand 834 members
el que son 12 mil 834 miembros
with this enough they have already
con esto basta
done it enough
ya lo han hecho basta
oh do you want to know how much there is of each one
ay queréis saber cuánto hay de cada
they betray there are one thousand and six of choo rita there are
delatan hay mil seis de choo rita hay
715 weapons there are 110 and kids 44
715 me armas hay 110 y chavalería 44
kids you have those four hey fra
chavalería tienes esos cuatro oye fra
gol without those kids I have to
gol sin esa chavalería te tengo que
follow you on social networks I will not do it
seguir en las redes sociales no te lo
thank you very much right here I take you I
muchísimas gracias verdad aquí os llevo
think that is enough already I already know that I have
yo creo que ya es suficiente ya yo ya sé
done it many times the one who
que lo he hecho muchas veces el que nos
makes us members already because he does not want to because
hace miembros ya porque no quiere porque
you have there are prices to give away
tienes hay precios para de para regalar
but already with this well if we
pero ya vaya ya con esto bueno si
reach 2000 there we can rest
llegamos a 2000 ahí nos podemos quedar
easy
tranquilo
if we reach 2000 we can rest
si llegamos a 2000 nos podemos quedar
easy and there are many people who pass
tranquilo y está mucha gente que pasa
that have totally passed the peters and
que ha pasado totalmente las peters y
girls of lost track many people to
muchachas de perdió la pista mucha gente
tie me from the track to the Sahara
a que me aten de la pista al sahara
welcome my weapon lost a lot
bienvenida mi arma perdido muchísimo se
lost track of many people
le perdió la pista a muchísima gente de
really that  youtube
verdad que youtube ya
things are already quite complicated with
la cosa está bastante complicada con los
video games,
videojuegos
an era in which I've done
una época en la que he hecho a todo el
everything to everyone, I've done it to everyone, everyone is already
mundo todo lo he hecho a todos todo el
gone, almost all the
mundo ya se ha ido casi la mayoría de
tweets but
tweets pero
I had
yo tuve
before there were more the majority will be older
antes había más la mayoría será mayor
but there are not many people on youtube
pero no hay mucha gente en youtube
yet
todavía
javi oliveiro is dedicated to and poking a
javi oliveiro se dedica a y pinchando a
certain youtuber to create sanse or
cierto youtuber para crear sanse o
piques and controversies to then
piques y controversias para después
make absurd caracas
hacer caracas absurdos
and what's the problem 1800 members
y cuál es el problema 1800 miembros
kids
chavales
being there they are not there the channels it makes me
estar ahí no están ahí los canales
laugh when later they
a mí me hace gracia cuando luego
criticize that is sálvame or this kind of
critican eso es sálvame o esta clase de
program
programa
and that I love every time they say that
y que me encanta cada vez que dicen eso
man there
tío
are many people who can say then you
hay mucha gente que se puede decir luego
criticize sálvame but here you
criticais al sálvame pero aquí te
mean with then criticism in the knowledge
refieres con luego críticas en el saber
because I do not criticize it danny thank you very much
porque yo no lo critico danny muchas
welcome do
gracias bienvenido
you realize that always well they
os dais cuenta que siempre bueno se
want to get in place them to the pse or sara
quieren meter colocarles al pse o sara
thank you very much welcome gorgeous
muchísimas gracias bienvenida guapísima
always says is that then criticism of
siempre dice es que luego críticas a
sálvame but criticism criticism one of the
sálvame pero crítica crítica uno de los
channels to reach and in two days
canales a alcanzar y en dos días cara
smiling face with lollipop sunglasses  lollipop lollipop lollipop lollipop lollipop lollipop lollipop
sonriendo con gafas de sol piruleta
then
piruleta piruleta piruleta luego
explained by him and I don't know how much he will have I will do
explicado por él y no sé cuánto tendrá
but I'm sure he has many thousands
haré pero seguro que tiene muchos miles
which he has 11 thousand
la cual tiene 11 mil
and there I have no idea I have no idea
y ahí no tengo ni idea no tengo ni idea
how many he has area is on facebook
de cuántos tiene área está en facebook
facebook there are also members here as
facebook también hay miembros aquí en
soon as he has nobody knows there is
cuanto tiene nadie lo sabe
welcome baby
hay bebé bienvenido
that evidently the people who
que eso evidentemente la gente que
criticize surely also don't see the
critica seguramente tampoco ve a los
sanse channels on youtube of sense
canales del sanse de youtube de sentido
and those guys don't realize that you are
y esos tipos no se dan cuenta que eres
a tornado if there is no salt or you create it and
un tornado si no hay sal se o lo creas y
if the sand is calm you move them
si la arena está calmada las mueves
exactly that a friend of mine
exactamente eso me lo decía un colega
formerly told me mexia is that you are always
antiguamente mexía es que estás siempre
stirring the hornet's nest goat already always
moviendo el avispero cabro ya siempre
although I am not the protagonist but I
aunque yo no sea el protagonista pero
am moving it here moving it
estoy moviendo por aquí moviendo por
there knowing how to
allá saber
do the same with the internet but not
hacer lo mismo con internet pero no ya
those who make these channels but the
los que hacen estos canales sino el
public that you also do it to cesc al
público que tú también lo hace a cesc al
sea but in console issues and
sea pero en temas de consola y también
you also get involved with other u2 see and it gets you into
te metes con otros u2 ver y te mete en
other things so in the end we all
otras movidas así que al final todos
do the gentleman cheer up it made me
hacemos al señor se anime a mí me hizo
laugh a lot
mucha gracia
jordi white  I think it was when he says
jordi white creo que fue cuando dice
interviewed troop pines now we have to
entrevistados tropa pinos ya hay que
manage it will be like it and showed daddy
administrar será me gusta y mostró papi
what our daddy does what he does is to the
que hace nuestro papi lo que hace es al
pse or colleague let's see if you understand it's not the
pse o colega a ver si os enteráis no es
ceo of youtubers well that's how it is to the seo
al ceo de youtubers bueno así es al seo
of youtube but it's to the pse or sex that
de youtube pero es al pse o del sexo que
youtubers do I don't know but that
hacen los youtubers no sé pero eso
salcedo also in the end or rather it's that
salcedo también al fin al cabo o sea es
everything in part almost everything to do a
que todo en parte casi todo hacerlo un
little solfeggio
poco de solfeo
but absurd of greene rangers
pero absurdo de greene rangers
welcome welcome to lata
bienvenido bienvenido a lata
to the public to the very young people
al público a la gente muy joven
public on google I looked at the statistics he
público en google lo miré la estadística
must have looked at the statistics
debió mirar las estadísticas
and sometimes a lover I already fixed the
y yo a veces un amante arreglo ya el
video for the main channel which is
vídeo para el canal principal que son
two thirty man already uploaded the video at
las dos y media tío ya subió el video a
one
la una
of the audience
de audiencia
70 percent is men worth 70
un 70 por ciento es hombre vale un 70
percent men
por ciento los hombres
the maximum age is between 18 and 25 and then it
la máxima edad es entre 18 y 25 y luego
follows almost the same from 25 to 35 sun
le sigue casi igual de 25 a 35 sol
welcome
bienvenido
to less than villeta Javier is a love
a menos de villeta javier es un amor
could you talk about the paper one day I
podrías hablar del papel un día
don't understand about dress
no entiendo de vestido se ha empleado
little time has been spent Gonzalo I
poco tiempo gonzalo
don't understand the  appetite for that had a
no entiendo el apetito para eso tenía un
friend who had a channel the other day we
amigo que tenía un canal que el otro día
were talking about precisely the
estuvimos hablando de precisamente el
one man when beaten his channel was
one man cuando batida su canal se
called the bases of the paper that was
llamaba las bases del papel que se
called but he already has the channel
llamaba pero ya tiene el canal
abandoned
abandonado
well there is the bivouac and backs that kid
bueno está el vivac y backs ese chaval
super things of paper I don't know if even
súper cosas de papel no sé si hasta
between that went up up
entre que subía subida subió
andy thank you very much of the paper I think
andy muchas gracias del papel yo creo
that the best channels that there are in this
que los mejores canales que hay en este
super chat goes to you good night well thank you
súper chat va para ti buenas noches pues
very much thank you very much of course it
muchas gracias muchísimas gracias claro
goes to me for whoever is going to go
que va para mí para quien va a ir
[ __ ] that was purple for whoever
carajote que estaba morado para quien
dances
baile
or messes with the bolillos who watch the
o se meten con los bolillos que ven el
sálvame already that thing is another kid
sálvame ya esa cosa es otro chiquillo
this was just born before
esto acaba de nacer antes de que
argument and there he is seeing that
argumento y ahí está viendo eso
the thumb says the blond who earns more
el pulgar dice el rubio que gana más
alone ad in a live tweet than
solo anuncio en un directo de tweets que
with a video of 7 million on youtube
con un vídeo de 7 millones en youtube
pause my Korean dramas for you handsome
pause mis dramas coreanos por ti guapo
a hug your Korean dramas that with
un abrazo tu dramas coreanos que con en
what you see well it's over here I don't
lo que veis bueno ya se acabó aquí no
believe it
me lo creo
the blond earns more than the blond earns more
el rubio gana más que el rubio gana más
with a with a live
con un con un directo
than with a video of 7 million
que con un vídeo de 7 millones
and so direct every day
y así directo todos los días
but that's already  That's next level, okay,
pero eso ya es eso ya es next level vale
that's not even knowing what you have, that's
eso ya es no saber ni lo que tienes eso
not even knowing what you have.
ya es que no sabe ni lo que tiene